Academic Affairs and Provost, Office of Senior V.P. for; Records ua500
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Bulletins, 1845 - 2017 May 17; 2; 11.75 cubic ft.; 65 captures
  - Catalogue, 1911 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Catalogue, 1911-1912 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Catalogue, 1912-1913 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Catalogue, 1913-1914 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Catalogue, 1914-1915 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Catalogue, 1915 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Catalogue, 1915-1916 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Catalogue, 1916-1917 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Catalogue, 1917 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Catalogue, 1918 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1917; 1918 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Catalogues, 1919; 1920 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1919; 1920 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Catalogue, 1921; 1922 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1921; 1922 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Annual Catalog, 1922-1928 (Volume 1)
  - Official Register, 1926-1930 (Volume 2)
  - Catalogues, 1923; 1924 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1923; 1924 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Catalogues, 1925; 1926 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1925; 1927 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Catalogues, 1927-1928 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Catalogues, 1928; 1929 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1928; 1929 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Catalogues, 1929; 1930 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Catalogues, 1930; 1931 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1930; 1931 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Annual Catalogues, 1932-1933 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1932; 1933 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Official Register Annual Catalog, 1933-1934; 1934-1935 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1934; 1935 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Official Register, 1935-1936; 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - The Albany Collegiate Center Catalogue, 1936-1937 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1936; 1937 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Official Register, 1937-1938; 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1938; 1939 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Official Register, 1939-1940; 1940-1941 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Summer Session Official Register (Official Catalog), 1940; 1941 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Official Catalog, 1941-1943; 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Summer Session Official Catalog, 1942; 1943 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Summer Session, 1944; 1945 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Official Catalog, 1944-1945; 1945-1946 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1946; 1947 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Annual Catalog, 1937-1938 (Volume 3)
  - Official Catalog, 1946-1947; 1947-1948 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1948; 1949 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Annual Catalog/ Official Catalog, 1948-1949; 1949-1950 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1950; 1957 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Annual Catalog, 1950-1951; 1951-1952 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1952; 1953 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - General Catalog, 1952-1953; 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1954; 1955 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - General Catalog, 1954-1955; 1955-1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1956; 1957 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - General Catalog, 1956-1957; 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Program in Public Administration Bulletin, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1958; 1959 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - General Catalog, 1958-1959; 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Studies Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Program in Public Administration Bulletin, 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1960; 1961 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - General Catalog, 1960-1961; 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Graduate Program in Public Administration Bulletin, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Studies Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Program- College of Education, 1961-1962 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Catalogs, 1960-1962 (Volume 4)
  - Catalogs, 1962-1963 (Volume 5)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Program, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - School of Public Affairs Preliminary Announcement, 1962-1963 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1962; 1963 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - General Catalog, 1962-1963; 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Graduate School of Public Affairs Academic Summer Programs, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - School of Public Affairs, 1963-1964 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Schools of Public Affairs Academic Summer Programs Bulletin, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - School of Public Affairs, 1964-1965 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Summer Session Official Register, 1964; 1965 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins, 1964-1966; 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - School of Social Welfare, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1965-1966 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Summer Bulletin, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Course Schedule and Catalog, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Summer Bulletin, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - School of Business- Graduate Programs and Graduate Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - School of Library Science Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins, 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Course Schedule and Catalog, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Summer Bulletin, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Schedule of Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses. Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - School of Library Science Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins and General Information, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - School of Criminal Justice Bulletin, 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Schedule of Courses ( includes catalog and schedule), 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Summer Bulletin, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Schedule of Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses. School of Graduate Studies Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - School of Library Science Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin and General Information, 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - School of Criminal Justice Bulletin, 1969-1971 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Schedule of Courses (includes catalog and Schedule), 1970 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Summer Sessions Bulletin, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Graduate Bulletins, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Bulletins, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening, and Saturday Program Graduate Studies Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - School of Library Science Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin and General Information, 1970-1971 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - School of Criminal Justice Bulletin, 1970-1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Summer Session Bulletin, 1971 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Graduate Bulletins, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening, and Saturday Program of Graduate Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - School of Library and Information Science Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1971- 1972 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, Courses, Programs, Regulations and General Information, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - State University of New York at Albany, Undergraduate Bulletin, Faculty and Staff, 1971-1972 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - School of Criminal Justice Bulletin, 1971-1973 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Summer Sessions Bulletin, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Bulletins, 1972-1974 (Volume 6)
  - State University of New York at Albany, Undergraduate Bulletin, Faculty and Staff, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Program of Graduate Studies, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - School of Business Graduate Information and Graduate Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - School of Public Affairs -Updated Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1972-1973 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Bulletins, 1972-1973; 1973-1974; 1974-1975 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - School of Criminal Justice Bulletin, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - School of Library and Information Science Bulletin, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - James E. Allen Collegiate Center Bulletin, 1972; 1973-1974; 1974-1975; 1975-1976 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Summer Sessions Bulletin, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - State University of New York at Albany, Faculty, and Staff, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Courses Program of Graduate Studies, 1973-1974 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Graduate Bulletins, 1973-1975; 1974-1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, Programs, Courses and Regulations, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - School of Criminal Justice Bulletin, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1973-1975 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - School of Nursing Bulletin, 1973-1975; 1975-1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Summer Session Bulletin, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Graduate Courses, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin- Courses, Programs, and Regulations/ General Information, 1974-1975 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - State University of New York at Albany, Faculty- Staff, 1974-1975 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - School of Library and Information Science Bulletin, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Part-Time College Study, 1974 September; 1978 June; 1984 May-1986 September (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1975 May (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1975 June (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1975 September (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Summer Session Bulletin, 1975 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening, and Saturday Graduate Courses, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - School of Criminal Justice Graduate Bulletin, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1975-1977 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins, 1975-1976 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Graduate Bulletins, 1975-1976; 1976-1977; 1977-1978; 1978-1979; 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1976 May (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1976 June (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listing, 1976 September (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - College of General Studies- Program Listings, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Graduate Courses, 1976 September (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Summer Session Bulletin, 1976 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1976-1977 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Graduate Bulletins, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - School of Library and Information Science, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1976-1978 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1977 May- June (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Official Bulletin, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Schedule of Late Afternoon, Evening and Saturday Graduate Courses, 1977 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - School of Criminal Justice Graduate Bulletin, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1977-1979 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins, 1977-1978; 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1978 May (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1978 September (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Schedule of Courses, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Simplified Admission to Graduate Courses. Graduate Evening Courses Selected Graduate Credit Courses after 5 p.m. Schedule of Late Afternoon, Evening, and Saturday Graduate Courses [LAES], 1978 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Official Bulletin, 1978 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - College of General Studies Fall Minicollege 78/79, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - School of Social Welfare- Continuing Education Project, 1978-1979 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - College of Arts and Sciences Graduate Bulletins, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - School of Education Bulletin, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - School of Library and Information Science Bulletin, 1978/1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - School of Public Affairs Bulletin, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - College of General Studies Spring Minicollege Program, 1979 May (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Evening and Simplified Adminissions Courses, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Official Bulletin, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Bulletins, 1979-1980 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - School of Criminal Justice Graduate Bulletin, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - School of Social Welfare Bulletin, 1979-1981 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1980 December (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1980 May- June (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1980 September (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Evening and Simplified Adminissions Courses, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Official Bulletin, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1980-1982 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Evening and Simplified Admissions Courses, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses Bulletin, 1981 May (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1981 May (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Official Bulletin, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Evemimg Umdergraduate and Graduate Credit Course, 1982 May (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1982 May (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit, 1982 June (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - School of Library and Information Sciences, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1982-1983 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1982-1984 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Opportunities, 1983 September (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses, 1983 September (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Official Bulletin, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - School of Business Graduate Bulletin, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - School of Library and Information Science Bulletin, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Courses Bulletin, 1984 May (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course, The Source, 1984 May (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, the Source, 1984 September (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Graduate Opportunities, 1984 May (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Graduate Evening and Simplified Adminissions Courses, 1984 September (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Official Bulletin, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - School of Social Welfare, 1984 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, The Sources, 1985 May (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - College of General Studies Non-Credit Course Listings, The Source, 1985 December (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Evening and Simplified Admissions Courses, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Official Bulletin, 1985 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1985-1986 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Evening and Simplified Admissions Courses, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Official Bulletin, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - School of Business Bulletin, 1986 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - School of Information and Library Science interim Catalog, 1986 April (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1986-1987 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Evening and Simplified Admissions Courses, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Official Bulletin, 1987 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - School of Social Welfare- Continuing Education Program, 1987 May (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Official Bulletin, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1988-1989 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1988-1990 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Official Bulletin, 1989 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1989-1990 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Official Bulletin, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1990-1991 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1990-1992 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Summer Session Official Bulletin, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1991-1992 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Official Bulletin, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Bulletins, 1993 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Official Bulletin, 1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1994-1995 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Official Bulletin, 1995 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1995-1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Summer Session Bulletin, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Bulletin, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Summer Sessions, Preliminary Schedule, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Summer Sessions, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Summer Sessions, Preliminary Schedule, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Summer Session, 1998 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Graduate Bulletin ( Dept. of History- Department of Theatre), 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Graduate Bulletin (General Policies + Depart. Of Africana Studies- Program in Hispanic + Italian Studies), 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Undergraduate Bulletin, 1998-1999 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Summer Session, Preliminary Schedule, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Summer Session, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Graduate Bulletin, University at Albany International- General Reproduced from Infernet Archives by G. Williams, Univ. Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Graduate Bulletin, College f Arts + Sciences: Africana Studies- Woman's Studies Reproduced from Internet Archives by G. Williams, Univ. Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Graduate Bulletin, School of Public Health Reproduced from Internet Archives by G.Williams, University Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Graduate Bulletin, School of Business Reproduced from Internet Archives by Geofrey Williams, Unic. Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Bulletin, School of Education Reproduced from Internet Archives by Geoffrey Williams, University Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Graduate Bulletin, Nelson A. Rockerfeller College of Public Affairs + Policy- Introduction Reproduced from Internet Archives by G. Williams, Univ. Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Graduate Bulletin, Rockefeller College: School of Criminal Justice Reproduced from the Internet Archives by G. Williams, Univ. Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Graduate Bulletin, Rockefeller College: Graduate School of Public Affairs Reproduced from Internet, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Graduate Bulletin, Rockefeller College: School of Information Science + Policy Reproduced from Internet Archives, by G. Williams, University Archivist, 1999-2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)